‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎I think
‎I really want to
‎get engaged to you.
‎Will you
‎be my fiancé?
‎My goodness.
‎My gosh.
‎You managed to make time to come.
‎Ma'am.
‎I'm so glad you could come.
‎I reserved you a seat, just in case.
‎The ceremony will start soon. ‎Let's go inside.
‎Oh, no.
‎Not only am I not family,
‎but I also know ‎Chairwoman Baek quite well.
‎If I were to suddenly show up ‎without notice,
‎she'll be taken aback.
‎I'll just do what I've always done
‎and watch from afar.
‎Yes, of course.
‎Do whatever makes you feel comfortable.
‎-Go on inside. ‎-I will.
‎-You'll stay? Then we'll talk later. ‎-Yes, don't worry.
‎EPISODE 9
‎two, three.
‎-Congratulations! ‎-Congratulations!
‎I wish you both happiness.
‎What a nice day.
‎Congratulations, Mother.
‎I did it.
‎I'll take some photos now.
‎-Ma'am, Mr. Ma, big smiles. ‎-Okay.
‎One, two, three.
‎Make an arch with your arms.
‎One arm each from both sides.
‎One, two, three.
‎Yes, wonderful. There we go.
‎Chairwoman, please join them.
‎And you too, ma'am.
‎Thank you for raising me well.
‎-What are you doing? ‎-What's gotten into him?
‎That's lovely. Look over here, please.
‎One, two, three.
‎Ma'am, you look a bit tense.
‎-Let's see a big smile. ‎-Okay.
‎-Big smile. ‎-Sure.
‎-No need to be nervous. ‎-Right.
‎Clench your fists a few times to relax.
‎ELDEST SON
‎How are you, son?
‎I'm fine.
‎Your flight to Korea
‎I'll return soon, ‎as soon as my business here is done.
‎Then
‎you're still in the US?
‎Yes.
‎I'll call when I get back.
‎-Can you make an arch? ‎-An arch?
‎Just like that.
‎-Round and round ‎-Round and round
‎Round and round
‎-I think that'll do. ‎-Mr. Bong.
‎Stand closer to each other.
‎-It's lovely here. ‎-Isn't it?
‎You have no idea how much effort I put
‎into finding this place ‎to celebrate our engagement.
‎Yeo-ri, they call this ‎the bridge that reflects the moon.
‎The bridge that reflects the moon?
‎Yes. Look over there.
‎There are moons floating on the water.
‎Oh, you're right.
‎The day I held your hand,
‎the moon was also shining brightly.
‎Do you remember?
‎Of course I remember.
‎When you saw ghosts for a full month,
‎it was tough, wasn't it?
‎No.
‎It wasn't tough at all, thanks to you.
‎I was actually grateful to the ghosts
‎because they brought me to you.
‎I mean it.
‎Wow, it's so pretty.
‎-Yeo-ri. ‎-Yes?
‎Today's a special day. ‎Is there anything you want to do?
‎I'm doing it right now.
‎Strolling with the man I like.
‎It would be nicer
‎if we could hold hands too, but still.
‎We can.
‎Not tonight,
‎but someday.
‎That day will definitely come.
‎We promised
‎to find a solution together, remember?
‎Then I'll need to recover ‎my memories first.
‎I just can't remember.
‎I must be too afraid
‎to face whatever happened.
‎We'll take our time ‎and do things one by one.
‎I'm right by your side.
‎And now that we're really engaged,
‎let's promise to tell each other ‎if anything's burdening us.
‎Okay?
‎Okay.
‎-It's really pretty. ‎-Yeah.
‎What was my mother doing there?
‎She headed straight to Reina Hotel ‎as soon as she landed.
‎Not even the secretaries knew
‎why she returned to Korea ‎ahead of schedule.
‎Find out why she came back ‎ahead of schedule.
‎Yes, sir. Will do.
‎I can always create new circumstances.
‎When that time comes,
‎the stake you hold could be of great help.
‎Have Director Gong give her a call
‎so that Director Ok can get prepared.
‎Yes, sir.
‎Mom, how long do we have to wait?
‎Siena Hall's at the center of attention ‎since Yeo-ri's engagement.
‎How do you know that? ‎Is there a response already?
‎I checked, of course.
‎Siena Hall's booked through to next year,
‎and everyone's talking about ‎Yeo-ri's dress and makeup.
‎Mom.
‎Shouldn't we shut this down ‎before the synergy gets out of hand?
‎You have a point.
‎If she gains momentum ‎from stronger profits and performance,
‎we'll be at a disadvantage.
‎Exactly.
‎What do we do then?
‎What do you think?
‎Use that brain of yours for once.
‎I am using my brain.
‎You never think.
‎You never use your brain,
‎-so I always have to-- ‎-She wants us to be quiet.
‎Hello, Director Gong.
‎Pardon?
‎Oh, my.
‎I didn't think ‎you'd make a decision so quickly.
‎Thank you so much.
‎Yes.
‎I promise you won't be disappointed.
‎Thank you again.
‎Yes, of course.
‎Goodbye then. Thank you.
‎What did he say?
‎Is Director Gong going to side with us?
‎Yeah.
‎If he's with us, does that mean ‎the other directors are in too?
‎You bet.
‎When will they start?
‎It's best to attack ‎when the enemy least expects it,
‎so right away.
‎Right now?
‎This is Ok Gye-hui.
‎Let's call an extraordinary ‎shareholders' meeting.
‎The agenda is
‎the removal of Cheon Yeo-ri, ‎CEO of Reina Hotel.
‎She isn't picking up.
‎Ok Gye-hui knows no fear.
‎I'm sorry.
‎It ended up coming to this.
‎No, I let my guard down too.
‎Who knew she'd strike ‎the day after your engagement ceremony?
‎How are things looking?
‎Those loyal to the former chairman ‎have sided with Director Ok,
‎putting us 3% behind in shares.
‎In the end, it'll most likely come down ‎to a 51 to 49 split.
‎How about
‎using the slush fund information ‎you obtained recently?
‎I've obtained information ‎that they amassed a slush fund
‎by purchasing artworks ‎to display in the hotel.
‎Yeeon Museum of Art is involved,
‎and so is Ha-ri's uncle, ‎Chief Prosecutor Ok Gye-dong.
‎That would work to our advantage. ‎Why not release it now?
‎Everything is still circumstantial.
‎We don't have anyone's confession ‎or proof to back the claim.
‎If we release it rashly ‎at a critical time like this,
‎we'll struggle to maintain ‎our stock price.
‎And with Chief Prosecutor ‎Ok Gye-dong on their side,
‎things could go badly
‎and the hotel and I could become targets.
‎I do remember something similar happened
‎during the former chairman's time.
‎The truth will eventually come out,
‎but it will take a long time.
‎In the meantime, ‎Reina and I'll be dragged through the mud.
‎Time isn't on our side.
‎I'll request an investigation ‎when the time is right.
‎Are there any shareholders ‎worth contacting?
‎Here's the list.
‎Let's contact as many as we can.
‎You'll do it yourself, ma'am?
‎I have to do whatever it takes.
‎Hello.
‎This is Cheon Yeo-ri, CEO of Reina.
‎How have you been?
‎Hello, Chairman. It's Baek Gyeong-ja.
‎Yes, I know.
‎I should've kept them in line ‎while I could.
‎I heard your child is clever and bright.
‎I hope they learn a great deal ‎and join our company.
‎Hi, Gang-uk.
‎Something came up at work.
‎Can I call you once things are settled?
‎Yes, of course. ‎Call me when you have time.
‎Thanks.
‎They're waiting for you inside.
‎Hello. Sorry for the delay.
‎Shall we sit down?
‎You've seen it once before,
‎how CEO Cheon's personal life ‎dragged down the stock price.
‎Let's drink.
‎-Do give us your full support. ‎-Gosh.
‎Don't worry, Chairwoman.
‎-Everything will work out. ‎-Thank you.
‎I'm sure you see ‎that she has her shortcomings,
‎so I hope you'll
‎No. Even so, sir--
‎Come in.
‎Ma'am?
‎Here's the information ‎you requested yesterday.
‎-Mr. Bong. ‎-Yes?
‎I'd like to contact her, ‎Han Se-in, in person.
‎Yes, ma'am.
‎Min-hwan.
‎You're here.
‎What's the occasion, ‎asking me to keep you company?
‎You mind?
‎Of course I don't.
‎You're surrounded by people.
‎I'm surprised, that's all.
‎You ignored so many of my calls until now.
‎Sorry.
‎I had a lot to sort out.
‎So? Did you sort everything out?
‎Almost.
‎Does that include Yeo-ri?
‎She must be having a tough time.
‎She is in a tough situation,
‎but I doubt things are bad for her.
‎Look at her.
‎Despite everything, ‎she quashed those rumors
‎and got engaged to that prosecutor.
‎I do admire her resilience.
‎How are you doing?
‎Let's drink.
‎You don't leave any openings, do you?
‎Neither do I.
‎Min-hwan.
‎If I were to replace Yeo-ri,
‎would you date me?
‎Yeo-ri will lose her position ‎after the shareholders' meeting.
‎It won't be as easy as you think.
‎She's Cheon Yeo-ri.
‎Be honest with me.
‎Is it that impossible to give up on her?
‎When did it all begin?
‎I'm not sure.
‎Ever since I was young,
‎I've always worried ‎about other people's feelings.
‎But with Yeo-ri
‎I didn't have to do that, ‎and I could relax around her.
‎That's why I grew to like her.
‎I thought she'd always stay ‎right where she was.
‎But when I came back
‎Before I give up for good
‎It may seem reckless, ‎but I might try something different.
‎It'll be my first and last attempt.
‎Ma'am, it's a call regarding Ms. Han.
‎Hello, Cheon Yeo-ri speaking.
‎She's out of the country?
‎Then where is she?
‎Yes.
‎Okay.
‎Is that so?
‎You can reach her by phone though, right?
‎Put me through ‎once you're able to reach her.
‎Thanks.
‎Gang-uk.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎I tried to be patient and wait,
‎but I couldn't reach you ‎when we'd just gotten engaged.
‎And I missed you.
‎I was also worried ‎that something was wrong.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎Did I do something wrong?
‎Is that what you were worried about?
‎I'm sorry. I should've called you.
‎What's going on?
‎It's not in the news yet,
‎but an extraordinary shareholders' meeting ‎will be held at Reina soon.
‎The main agenda will be my removal.
‎That's why things were a bit crazy.
‎Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
‎I thought our engagement ‎helped secure your position.
‎Is it a serious situation?
‎I'm trying my best ‎to persuade the shareholders,
‎but things don't look great.
‎It looks like I might have to ‎stay here all night.
‎I'll stay with you.
‎No. You can't do that.
‎Why not? I belong right by your side.
‎If there's not much I can do, ‎I'll run coffee errands.
‎I make pretty good coffee.
‎CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‎FRIENDLY, HOSTILE, NEUTRAL
‎Yeo-ri. You can take your gloves off ‎when you're with me.
‎I'll be careful.
‎Okay.
‎Who is this person that you're so
‎REINA HOLDINGS ‎MAJOR SHAREHOLDERS CHECKLIST
‎CKO Construction is one of ‎Reina Holdings' major shareholders.
‎One of the chairman's sons got divorced
‎and the former daughter-in-law ‎received some shares.
‎-That's Han Se-in? ‎-Yeah.
‎So I'm gathering information ‎to find a way to win her over.
‎Her father is Han Jeong-eup.
‎I heard that name somewhere.
‎Do you know Chaeum Artrion?
‎He built that.
‎I know. My mom took me there ‎to see shows when I was young.
‎As an adult, ‎I went a few times with my grandma.
‎She must have ‎a lot of memories there with you.
‎Of course. She loved going there.
‎Since CKO Construction is owned ‎by her former in-laws,
‎I'm hoping Ms. Han ‎will make a different vote.
‎So I'm waiting to hear from her.
‎Ma'am!
‎Ma'am.
‎I didn't see anything.
‎But that's not what's important.
‎Ms. Han is currently residing ‎in Singapore.
‎What?
‎She runs her own business there
‎and actively holds exhibitions too.
‎What kind of exhibitions do you mean?
‎Well, I heard
‎She's an art director ‎or something of the kind.
‎It's all here.
‎Her name is also on the list of attendees
‎of the hotel investment conference ‎that you held off on attending.
‎Is that so?
‎Put me through to her ‎as soon as you reach her.
‎Yes, will do.
‎I'll see myself out then.
‎She seems to be closely aligned ‎with our interests.
‎I think we've got a good shot.
‎Ma'am, I'm coming in!
‎I'm sorry, ma'am.
‎We got a call from Ms. Han.
‎Hello.
‎This is Cheon Yeo-ri of Reina.
‎I'm going abroad on a business trip.
‎I understand that it's a conference ‎to attract investors,
‎but why go now ‎if it won't bring immediate results?
‎Are you confident you can manage?
‎Yes.
‎Please keep up the work on your end.
‎I'll stay in touch ‎with any shareholders I can reach,
‎even while I'm abroad.
‎Will you be able to return on time?
‎Of course.
‎Yeo-ri's going abroad for business ‎at a time like this?
‎I got an invitation to it too.
‎It is a pretty large-scale conference ‎as far as attracting investment goes.
‎I get why she wants to go,
‎but why go now at a time like this?
‎Yeo-ri must feel cornered ‎to resort to something this ridiculous.
‎She'd likely lose her position ‎if the vote were tomorrow.
‎Even if she makes a deal there, ‎she'd only have time to sign an MOU.
‎It's quite an odd move.
‎Have our people look into it.
‎This is the list of attendees ‎for the Singapore conference.
‎The sole agenda of the upcoming ‎general meeting is her removal,
‎yet she's traveling abroad for business?
‎Compile a list of shareholders ‎who recently transferred their shares.
‎Yes, sir.
‎I'm too worried about you ‎going abroad on your own.
‎There's nothing to worry about. ‎I'll be just fine.
‎No, not about you. ‎I'm worried about myself.
‎I'm already dreading the thought ‎of not seeing you for days.
‎Then come with me.
‎Don't prosecutors go abroad ‎on business trips?
‎There are global seminars and conferences. ‎Should I actually look into it?
‎Leave it. I won't be away for long.
‎Okay.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎I'll come to the airport to see you off.
‎Man, I barely finished it in time.
‎Hold on.
‎There's more?
‎Silly me.
‎-You should've handed it over earlier. ‎-Mr. Ma.
‎What's all that?
‎The Case Division assigned us some cases.
‎Why today, of all days
‎Oh, man.
‎Come on!
‎Why are there so many?
‎Ms. Eom is already there ‎and arranging meetings on her end.
‎I'll keep you updated
‎if anything needs to be arranged ‎on this end.
‎Take good care of my grandmother ‎until I come back.
‎Please don't worry. ‎Remember, I'm Bong Ji-uk.
‎Ma'am.
‎Good luck.
‎Thank you.
‎Of course.
‎-Yeo-ri. ‎-Oh.
‎-Gang-uk. ‎-Hello.
‎Hello.
‎-Mr. Bong, wait. ‎-Yes?
‎Oh, dear. Sorry.
‎Weren't you busy with work?
‎Don't worry about my work. ‎I'd take you to Singapore if I could.
‎Huh?
‎What's going on?
‎Why? What is it?
‎Is Kang Min-hwan going too?
‎I didn't know he was going.
‎Should I go too?
‎I think I should come with you.
‎Don't be silly.
‎I'll be fine.
‎Call me if something happens, okay?
‎I'll fly right over to see you.
‎Promise me, okay?
‎Sure.
‎-Hyeong-min, that thing from last time. ‎-What?
‎Is this year's International Association ‎of Prosecutors event in Singapore?
‎It has to be, okay? Pull up the notice.
‎-Yeah, that one. ‎-It is happening in Singapore.
‎"Prosecution organizations ‎and personnel from around the world
‎gather to discuss ‎ideal criminal legislation."
‎It's open to well-rounded prosecutors.
‎That's me. This is perfect.
‎Sign me up immediately.
‎Forget it. ‎Don't even dream of going abroad.
‎You refused to go because ‎you didn't want to write an extra report.
‎No, not anymore.
‎I'll write up a killer report. ‎Hyeong-min, sign me up right now.
‎-I can't. ‎-What?
‎Applications were due yesterday.
‎There's a conference in Thailand ‎to review international law.
‎Yes, there is.
‎Call up the organization hosting that
‎and have them host it ‎in Singapore instead, okay?
‎What?
‎Let's say they move it to Singapore ‎and all you have to do is go.
‎But today is your turn
‎to handle the night shift.
‎You forgot?
‎Oh, jeez.
‎You forgot.
‎Let's go, sir.
‎Will you attend the reception later?
‎Most of the investors will be there.
‎Of course. I'll be there.
‎Hello?
‎Ma'am, I just heard from Ms. Han.
‎She wants to meet you an hour later.
‎Did she say why?
‎I asked, but she only said ‎it was personal.
‎I didn't want to upset her ‎before negotiations,
‎so I said you'd agree to the delay.
‎I apologize.
‎I understand. Bye.
‎Are you Ms. Cheon?
‎Hello, Ms. Han.
‎I was surprised to get your call.
‎You came all the way here ‎to meet me over my 3% stake?
‎I wanted to meet you in person.
‎I did some research myself.
‎Some want you removed
‎because of your scandals ‎and poor management skills.
‎I can't say I've been perfect ‎at every turn,
‎but I can't accept the claim
‎that I mismanaged the company ‎enough to warrant a removal motion.
‎I can prove it with objective numbers.
‎Would you take a look?
‎I'll be honest with you.
‎The truth is,
‎someone made me a bold offer ‎just an hour ago.
‎They offered double ‎the current market price for my shares.
‎-They offered double? ‎-So I agreed to transfer them.
‎What?
‎Was it one of Director Ok's people?
‎No.
‎I have to keep their identity undisclosed ‎until the deal is signed.
‎From my perspective,
‎I have no reason to turn down the offer.
‎Ms. Han.
‎From what I see,
‎it's just a mudslinging fight ‎between family members.
‎Doesn't it all end up the same, ‎whoever becomes CEO?
‎You must know how things are, Ms. Han.
‎Fights like these.
‎You went through a legal dispute ‎with your younger brother.
‎Let's leave my family out of this ‎when it's about yours.
‎To be truthful, I have no interest
‎in your fight to defend your position.
‎I'm busy enough ‎running my own business here.
‎I'm here for your business ‎interests as well.
‎I don't see you
‎as a mere shareholder ‎or someone whose shares I need to acquire.
‎I want us to build our careers together
‎through our shared passion for art.
‎If you side with me this time,
‎I'll give you the right to curate ‎and host exhibitions anywhere you want.
‎That includes both
‎Reina's domestic and overseas affiliates.
‎With such authority,
‎you may not be able to ‎double your investment right away,
‎but the profit you stand to gain ‎in a few years will be much greater.
‎That is a very alluring offer.
‎It could boost my career too.
‎But I care more about my immediate reality
‎than the distant future.
‎Thank you for the offer, ‎but I'll have to decline.
‎-Ms. Han. ‎-I'm sorry.
‎Just a moment.
‎Can you hear me out a little more
‎before you make up your mind?
‎Well, I've already made up my mind.
‎I don't think talking any further ‎will change anything.
‎But still
‎Are you all right, ma'am?
‎Find out if Ms. Han will ‎attend the reception tonight.
‎I already checked. ‎Her name is on the list.
‎Are you all right?
‎I heard your company's struggling.
‎The company is fine. ‎I'm the one struggling.
‎That's why I came all this way.
‎I'm sure you'll manage. ‎You're Cheon Yeo-ri.
‎Apparently, it's some kind of ‎mystical object.
‎Ji-hwan!
‎You have to live.
‎I'll die instead.
‎12 YEARS AGO
‎Hold this for me.
‎Oh, come on. In this day and age,
‎you really think wearing that ‎will keep ghosts away?
‎Look. My grandma said something ‎about this pendant.
‎Apparently, it's some kind of ‎mystical object.
‎Hey, I'm being serious.
‎My grandma acts like ‎it's the end of the world
‎if I so much as take it off.
‎Well, it's not like ‎there's no way to confirm it.
‎I believe you.
‎Why don't you try wearing it?
‎-Me? ‎-I have a feeling
‎it'll suit you way better than me.
‎You know, necklaces like this
‎look better when worn by someone pretty.
‎It looks great on you.
‎You can keep it.
‎Really?
‎But what if something happens to you?
‎That's just my luck then.
‎I don't mind it ‎if it means I can save you.
‎-What? ‎-If something does happen,
‎you have to live. I'll die instead.
‎Why would you say something like that?
‎Are you okay? Oh, jeez.
‎Wait here. ‎I'll get something to wipe you dry.
‎Okay.
‎Is something wrong?
‎Let me see
‎-Do we have any tissues? ‎-Tissues?
‎I don't know. I don't see any.
‎There aren't any here.
‎Ji-hwan!
‎Yeo-ri!
‎What if something happens to you?
‎I don't mind it ‎if it means I can save you.
‎If something does happen,
‎you have to live. I'll die instead.
‎The pendant.
‎Are you okay?
‎Yeah.
‎I'd forgotten
‎a lot of the memories from back then.
‎Do you remember Ji-hwan's pendant
‎from the accident 12 years ago?
‎What pendant?
‎The necklace. ‎Ji-hwan put it on me that day.
‎I was wearing it.
‎Do you know if it was ‎among his belongings?
‎I'm not sure.
‎If you were wearing it,
‎maybe you lost it ‎when you fell into the sea?
‎Did I?
‎Ma'am.
‎Excuse me.
‎It's about Ms. Han.
‎She checked out of the hotel ‎30 minutes before this reception.
‎What?
‎Let's go.
‎Ms. Cheon was in continued contact ‎with a woman named Han Se-in in Singapore.
‎CKO CONSTRUCTION, HAN SE-IN, NEUTRAL
‎She owns exactly 3%.
‎I'm quite surprised and also flustered.
‎You're offering double the market price?
‎A card has the greatest impact
‎when it's played ‎at the most unexpected moment.
‎That is true.
‎So is this the reason
‎you asked me to delay my meeting ‎with Ms. Cheon by an hour?
‎A deal is best when offered first.
‎I have just one condition.
‎Until the deal is finalized,
‎you are to keep ‎the buyer's identity undisclosed.
‎That's all I ask.
‎Have you called her?
‎She's not answering. ‎I think she's avoiding the calls.
‎First, call Mr. Bong.
‎Tell him to put a team together ‎and find out what Ms. Han is up to.
‎Yes, ma'am.
‎Wait a minute.
‎Ms. Han has nothing to do ‎with hotel investment.
‎Yet she was invited to this event.
‎I'll look into who invited her here.
‎I love this.
‎Is this much okay?
‎Man, it's not here. Where is it?
‎What's this?
‎He never said a word to me.
‎Give me that.
‎Why do you have this?
‎-Do you ‎-It's not like that.
‎What do you mean?
‎Min-hwan.
‎Have you lied to me all along?
‎What did I lie about?
‎You asked me if I'd asked Yeo-ri out.
‎You said the matching rings were too much.
‎You lied whenever I asked ‎because you had an ulterior motive.
‎I didn't lie about anything.
‎And I don't have to explain ‎my feelings to you.
‎I don't want to argue with you about this.
‎That's your problem.
‎If there's something wrong, talk about it.
‎Why do you always avoid the situation?
‎Min-hwan.
‎Min-hwan!
‎Kang Min-hwan.
‎Want me to tell you ‎why I avoid the situation?
‎I can argue with you about anything,
‎but nothing will change.
‎What won't change?
‎If I so much as raise my voice at you,
‎do you know how our family looks at me?
‎What do you mean?
‎Tell me. How do they look at you?
‎Forget it. I've had enough.
‎Do you have some kind of victim mentality?
‎What?
‎What's wrong?
‎It's still a zero-sum game.
‎If we take shares from them, ‎they take shares from us.
‎We still don't know ‎what Ms. Han is up to, do we?
‎Yes.
‎Keep looking into it.
‎Bye.
‎INCOMING CALL
‎Hello? Yeo-ri?
‎You're still awake.
‎I was worried you'd be asleep.
‎I wouldn't be asleep.
‎How are things going on your end?
‎Not too well, to be honest.
‎She turned me down at our first meeting,
‎and she's been ignoring us since then.
‎She left without a trace.
‎Man, that's not good. ‎You must've been flustered.
‎Which is why, Gang-uk,
‎I need to ask for a favor.
‎I gave it a lot of thought ‎before calling you.
‎Of course, tell me what you need. ‎I'll help with anything.
‎First, there's something ‎I'd like you to pass to my secretary.
‎-Okay. ‎-And the other favor is
‎Could you help us locate Han Se-in?
‎I do have a team looking for her,
‎but we're short on time.
‎I can totally do that.
‎I know a guy ‎whose specialty is finding people.
‎I'll call him right away.
‎Thank--
‎What's this about?
‎Hyeong-min, ‎I'm all sorts of urgent right now.
‎I racked my brain ‎and you're the only one I could think of.
‎What do you want me to do?
‎-No way. I won't do it. ‎-Come on.
‎From the sushi restaurant nearby ‎that you love so much,
‎I brought an assortment ‎of the freshest-looking sushi.
‎Look.
‎-Mr. Ma, what do you take me for? ‎-Yeah?
‎Do you think ‎a few pieces of sushi would
‎-Shall I have a taste? ‎-Yeah. Sit down.
‎-Is this it? ‎-Yeah, that's it.
‎BREATHING NEW LIFE INTO OLD PAINTINGS
‎Here, open wide.
‎Okay.
‎Want the eel next?
‎Here.
‎-She was in Singapore until recently. ‎-Okay.
‎The photos on her social media
‎show the exhibition venues ‎and the art she handled.
‎-This lady, though. ‎-Yeah?
‎She must have a personal account ‎aside from this official one.
‎You think so?
‎Hold on.
‎Here, open up.
‎-Here? Or lower? ‎-Yes, there.
‎-No, that side. ‎-This side?
‎Your muscles are so tense.
‎It's illegal to look up ‎one's credit card transactions.
‎There's a limit to what I can find ‎on social media alone.
‎Hyeong-min, that's exactly why ‎I came to you for help.
‎On to your right shoulder.
‎My gosh, this side is even worse.
‎Mr. Ma.
‎-Mr. Ma. ‎-Huh?
‎Take a look at this.
‎The same photo ‎keeps appearing on her feed.
‎She seems to post it ‎whenever it comes to mind.
‎Take a look.
‎This place is
‎What time is it?
‎I need to call that elder.
‎Madam Pang?
‎-Hyeong-min, I have a flight to catch. ‎-Okay.
‎-Call me when you have something, okay? ‎-What?
‎Thanks a lot. ‎Clean up after yourself. I love you.
‎Mr. Ma.
‎You punk.
‎He got me again.
‎Thank you.
‎Hello, Mr. Bong.
‎I just got it. All right.
‎He's not there either?
‎Okay then.
‎I understand. Okay, bye.
‎If he's not in Ms. Im's office, ‎he's not in the building.
‎Where else could he be? His grandmother's? ‎No, she seemed clueless.
‎He's never been late for work.
‎It's eleven o'clock now, so where is he?
‎Where on earth is he? Why--
‎-Ma Gang-uk, this punk ‎-Sir.
‎He's over at
‎He went to Mr. Hwang's office.
‎What are you on about? ‎That's where I'm coming from.
‎-You see, Ma-- ‎-Yes. He was there,
‎then he went to the bathroom. ‎The men's, of course.
‎He had a stomachache this morning.
‎If it's urgent, I'll pass it to him
‎-in the bath-- ‎-What's with you?
‎That punk called me at the crack of dawn
‎and said he needed to take three days off.
‎He just does whatever he pleases.
‎Is something going on?
‎-You don't know, do you? ‎-Well
‎I signed it, so process it.
‎That troublemaker.
‎LEAVE REQUEST: MA GANG-UK
‎He took three days off.
‎Why didn't he tell us? Where did he go?
‎He went to Singapore.
‎He actually went?
‎After all that fuss, he actually went?
‎What on earth is going on?
‎Why didn't you tell me anything?
‎I figured if I knew, ‎there was no way you didn't
‎I thought you'd know. I'm sorry.
‎I stayed up working on something ‎with Mr. Ma,
‎so I was a bit out of it this morning.
‎You two stayed up last night without me?
‎Yes.
‎How come? Why wasn't I there?
‎Why wasn't I included? ‎That's not fair. I'm hurt.
‎Why would you feel hurt?
‎You should be glad
‎you didn't have to suffer ‎and stay up working.
‎We only ate spicy rice cakes. That's it.
‎Man, I'm tired.
‎I saw traces of sushi.
‎We had pizza too.
‎I saw you had blood sausage too.
‎-I swear I cleaned up. ‎-Darn you.
‎-How could you? ‎-Okay. I'll treat you.
‎I'll kill you if I catch you again.
‎Goodness, Yeo-ri is all you talk about.
‎Does she know you're like this?
‎I might tell her on this trip.
‎Yes, hello.
‎I'd like to see you.
‎Ma'am.
‎A private investor called Danny Tan ‎invited Ms. Han.
‎I just arranged a meeting with him.
‎-Is that so? ‎-Yes.
‎He wants to meet you ‎at the aquarium at 3 p.m.
‎Okay. Good work.
‎It's lovely here, ‎whatever time of year I visit.
‎I love it here as well.
‎The view is extra special today.
‎And the tea tastes even better ‎with you here, Ms. Song.
‎Take a nice walk around the grounds,
‎and stay for dinner as well.
‎Is Mr. Ma doing well?
‎I only saw him from afar,
‎but he seemed to be doing well.
‎He's so busy with work.
‎I got a call from him ‎the day after the ceremony
‎and nothing since.
‎Actually, I asked to see you because
‎Yes, of course. I'm listening.
‎Well
‎Could you arrange for me ‎to meet Mr. Ma over a meal?
‎You can introduce me ‎as a close acquaintance.
‎Yes, of course. I can do that.
‎I'll arrange something, ‎then call you right away.
‎By the way,
‎you said you're well-acquainted ‎with his fiancée's grandmother.
‎We're in the same field, ‎as you already know.
‎Yeo-ri and Ji-hwan were friends ‎since they were young,
‎and they went to the same school too.
‎Oh, they were friends?
‎They're not the same age, are they?
‎Ji-hwan was born ‎in the year of the monkey,
‎and Yeo-ri was born ‎in the year of the goat.
‎That can't be.
‎Yeo-ri and Ji-hwan are the same age.
‎Whose is this?
‎MAY 8, 1991, 18:00 ‎FEMALE, YEAR OF THE GOAT
‎Could it be
‎No need for excuses.
‎That date and time of birth.
‎Who does it really belong to?
‎Oh, right. This
‎This is my wife's date of birth.
‎You see
‎Okay. I'm really sorry.
‎What am I to do with that punk?
‎Perhaps I could explain
‎Make an excuse? ‎I wouldn't call it an excuse.
‎Gang-uk was really stressed out over this,
‎and he kept letting out deep sighs.
‎Since I'm older than him, ‎I wanted to help him out.
‎For their love, their true love
‎Enough.
‎So,
‎where is Gang-uk right now?
‎Hello?
‎Ma'am, it's about Danny Tan.
‎He called to say he had to attend ‎another urgent meeting.
‎What should I do?
‎All right. Bye.
‎Gang-uk.
‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎I missed you so much, Yeo-ri.
‎I'm glad you're here with me.
‎-Cheers. ‎-Cheers.
‎Want to come in for a cup of tea?
‎How can I be sure that my 3% ‎will be enough for you to win?
‎You're desperate.
‎Don't you want to protect it?
‎We will now begin the extraordinary ‎general meeting of shareholders
‎regarding the motion for removal ‎of Reina Hotel's CEO, Cheon Yeo-ri.
‎Then Cheon Yeo-ri will ‎no longer have a hold on Reina.
‎Ma Gang-uk, was it?
‎Is he giving you trouble?
‎What's going on here?
‎You've been reassigned ‎to an overseas training program.
‎Gang-uk is
‎going abroad?
‎Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim